<html>
	<meta>
		<resource>
			<type/>
			<id type="isbn-10" value="1118508815"/>
			<url site="www.wowebook.be">http://www.wowebook.be/book/siri-for-dummies/</url>
		</resource>
		<site>www.wowebook.be</site>
		<source>http://www.wowebook.be/book/siri-for-dummies/</source>
		<download-date>2012-12-20 18:32:43</download-date>
	</meta>
	<book structure_version="1">
		<title>Siri For Dummies </title>
		<content>
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Book Description&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Find out what Siri&#8217;s got up her sleeve with this fun and friendly guide!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who couldn&#8217;t use a little extra help these days? Answers, information, reminders, and all sorts of additional help are only a verbal query away with Siri, the artificial intelligence personal assistant. Siri made her debut with the iPhone 4 and is now updated for iOS 6 as well as the third-generation iPad and she is ready to assist! This easy-to-understand guide walks you through the vast array of capabilities that Siri boasts, from creating texts and e-mails from dictation to getting directions to finding a restaurant in the area. You&#8217;ll discover how to check the weather, get sports scores and schedules, look up a movie review, get Facebook and Twitter updates, make dinner reservations, and much more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Explains how to finesse the perfectly worded questions for Siri in order to get the most helpful and accurate answers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Details how to have Siri make phone calls for you, look up information in a dictionary or on the web, or get music&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Walks you through using Siri to get stock quotes or enter numbers into a calculator and get an answer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shows you how to use Siri to set reminders and alarms, take notes, get turn-by-turn driving directions, and more&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just like Siri, the straightforward-but-fun &lt;em&gt;Siri For Dummies&lt;/em&gt; is here to help you!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span id="more-22719"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the Back Cover&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Learn to:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Search the web, schedule appointments, and set reminders&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use your voice to create texts, e-mails, and Facebook posts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Find movie times and watch trailers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Make restaurant reservations, check sports scores, and more&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Siri is utterly awesome! Make the most of her skills with the advice in this book She&#8217;s such a charmer, that Siri! Here&#8217;s how to use your voice-activated assistant to help you review texts and e-mails, take dictation, navigate city streets, find the nearest Chinese restaurant and reserve a table, and get the weather report, sports scores, movie times, and more. Learn all the ways Siri can get you organized, entertain you, and save you time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Organize your life &#8212; let Siri schedule your appointments, move them, keep you on time, and sync your calendar with other devices&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Never be lost &#8212; get turn-by-turn directions to an address across town or across the country&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get reviews &#8212; let Siri help you choose a movie or find great sushi within your budget&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Take a letter &#8212; dictate your e-mail or text messages and have Siri send them&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Find answers &#8212; ask Siri to define a word, solve a math problem, or tell you who won the game&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Social Siri &#8212; post to Facebook&#174;, send tweets, and find your friends with Siri&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open the book and find:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;How Siri understands your natural speech&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The many ways Siri can speed up mundane tasks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to launch your favorite apps with Siri&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Help setting location-based reminders&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ways Siri can entertain you&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All about web-searching with Siri&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to make Siri your DJ&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tips for adding punctuation to your texts and e-mails&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tips for getting walking directions and finding landmarks and other points of interest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
		</content>
		<images>
			<item>http://img.wowebook.com/images/497229225.jpg</item>
		</images>
		<details>
			<release>November 2012</release>
			<format type="paperback/ebook">
				<pages> 264 pages</pages>
				<size>[66.8 MB] </size>
			</format>
			<author/>
			<language>English</language>
			<isbn>
				<item type="ISBN-10" value="1118508815"/>
				<item type="ISBN-13" value="978-1118508817"/>
			</isbn>
		</details>
		<categories>
			<tag site="wowebook.be" value="For Dummies"/>
			<tag site="wowebook.be" value="game"/>
			<tag site="wowebook.be" value="Social"/>
			<tag site="wowebook.be" value="Facebook"/>
			<tag site="wowebook.be" value="For Dummies"/>
			<tag site="wowebook.be" value="iOS"/>
			<tag site="wowebook.be" value="iPad"/>
			<tag site="wowebook.be" value="iPhone"/>
			<tag site="wowebook.be" value="Siri"/>
			<tag site="wowebook.be" value="Social"/>
			<tag site="wowebook.be" value="Twitter"/>
		</categories>
		<download>
			<link>
				<text>For.Dummies.Siri.For.Dummies.Nov.2012.epub</text>
				<url>http://adf.ly/1409722/http://prefiles.com/1y8wyrrrccxl/For.Dummies.Siri.For.Dummies.Nov.2012.epub.html</url>
				<text2>Download from PreFiles.com</text2>
			</link>
		</download>
	</book>
</html>